I took her hearing offline.
[Kirsh] She mentioned a sound
the moment we landed.
It was louder the closer
to the Xenomorph she got.
Then last night in the lab
when I extracted the embryo…
You think it's got something
to do with these creatures?
Not all of them. Just one species.
[Dame Sylvia] Hmm.
[vocalizing] Ma. Ah. Ah. Ah.
[sighs] Stop frowning. It's not a wake.
We're on a voyage of discovery,
and I have a colonic in 30 minutes.
Go, uh, push some buttons and turn some
knobs while the grown-ups talk.
We've taken her offline.
We think she can hear--
The Xenomorph, yeah. Just assume
I'm ahead of you always.
Which… Don't you have little, you know,
little experiments to run?
These creatures
aren't gonna discover themselves.
Of course.
You too.
No. She's scared. She needs me.
Ah, careful. You're not her mother.
It's an IT issue, not a gab session.
And I'm still waiting on your field
assessments of the hybrid performance.
I'll be back. Okay?
[sighs] Alone at last.
Okay.
Let's bring her hearing online…
[beeping rapidly, stops]
…figure out
if it's a hardware or a software issue.
-Oh, good. It's the brother.
-Are you okay?
-Uh, she can't hear you.
-[exhales sharply]
-Why?
-Uh, we took her hearing offline.
-He did what?
-Hi.
We haven't met. You, uh…
You work f-for me.
Or should I say you work for a, uh,
subsidiary of a subsidiary of
a holding company of an LLC of mine.
Yeah, how's the new lung?
[stammers] It's great. Thanks.
You'll never guess
what we did with the old one.
-What?
-I can't hear you.
I can't hear.
There was a-a sound in the lab.
It hurt my head. I-I can't hear.
Okay. [chuckles]
What's in the lab?
[smacks lips]
Tell me you didn't bring
those things back here.
We're wasting time. Okay, bring
her audio processors online.
Yeah. [clears throat] Okay.
[sighs] All right. Can you hear my voice?
[muffled] Can you hear my voice?
Can you hear my voice?
-Yeah. Yeah. [chuckles]
-Yeah? Can you hear the sound?
-No.
-[Arthur] No? Okay, how's this?
-Okay. Okay.
-Okay?
-Okay. [laughing]
-Okay.
Hey. Hey, Biscuit.
Hi.
Where were you?
I… I had a surgery,
but it's okay. I'm fine.
-[Arthur] Wendy.
-I'm all better.
-Hmm?
Can you tell me what happened?
I woke up and I heard it. The sound like…
[chirring]
Like bugs rubbing their legs together.
-Crickets?
-Hmm.
So I followed it. And it was coming
from the lab.
Kirsh was…
Kirsh was doing things in there.
He was experimenting on the eggs.
-[tearing]
-[chirring]
It was screaming.
[Hermit] The eggs?
No.
The baby.
-The baby was screaming.
-[squealing]
Okay, we're gonna figure out what it is
you're hearing and why you're hearing it,
and we're gonna make it stop.
-No.
[scoffs]
-What-What do you mean no?
-She… [scoffs]
…She can hear an alien language
and you wanna turn that off?
If it's hurting you,
we should make it stop.
No, I-I think they picked me.
-They're talking to me. I wanna hear them.
-Deal. Start the test.
[sighs] Okay.
Let's start the test at 20,000 Hz.
[chirring]
I hear it.
Okay, that's on low. What if I raise it?
Same.
Must be spread
across multiple frequencies.
Uh, I'm gonna go to the highest range now.
-[chirring sound escalating]
-[ticking]
-Stop, stop, stop, stop. Down.
-Down.
There.
[snaps fingers]
Curly, did you hear anything?
-Like what?
-A sound you can't identify.
Maybe.
Don't tell me what I wanna hear.
Tell me the truth.
Move.
Can you make the sound
in a frequency we can hear?
How?
How did you hack the data
to watch your brother? Hmm?
Asimov said above a certain level
technology
is indistinguishable from magic.
Don't think of your voice as a voice.
Think of it as a speaker,
just plays music.
The sound is in your mainframe,
so you just… [blows] …Alakazam.
[whirs]
[chirring]
[chirring continues]
[taps, exhales]
Sure you speak French,
but can you do that?
-Enough.
-[chirring continues]
-Oh, the brother's having a feeling.
-She needs to rest.
She has a lithium-ion battery
that could power a small city.
She doesn't need to rest. [chuckles]
She's not a machine.
She is a child and she's frightened.
I can speak for myself.
She-She needs a break, sir.
[stammers] It's been a rough night.
Of course.
Just take all the time you need.
Wanna go show me your room?
Yeah.
[exhales deeply]
What do you think?
I think when a hostile alien species
decides to speak, one needs to ask why.
Yeah, unless it's not her they're talking
to, it's each other and she can hear them.
-And now they know that too.
-[chuckles]
Are you sure you wouldn't like
to return them to Yutani
and get back to the work at hand?
So I can wake up one day with
a Xenomorph in my belly? No, thank you.
Tell the brother he can stay,
but he's working for us.
-The conflict.
-No.
Just a reminder.
It's my world. He just lives in it.
[rain falling]
I've been drawing a lot.
And, uh… and this is my bed.
Well, it's more like a charging station,
but it… it's kind of like a bed.
[chuckles]
You don't sleep?
Oh, I… [stammers]
No, not really. [chuckles]
Are you mad at me?
[chuckling] What?
Why would I be mad at you?
Because I wanted to hear the aliens. I…
Because you had
to go to a cemetery. For me.
No.
Come on.
I'm not mad at you.
I'm mad at them.
Why?
Because they wouldn't let me see you
when you were in the hospital.
Or Dad.
So you wanted to come?
Of course I wanted to come.
You just… You couldn't find a way?
If there was a way, I would have found it.
But there was a war,
and I was on the other side of the earth.
Okay.
I'm here now though.
[chuckles]
[Boy Kavalier] "The Neverland had been
make-believe in those days,
but it was real now…
and there were no night-lights,
and it was getting darker every moment."
-[slightly sobbing]
-[Morrow] When is a machine not a machine?
[Slightly] Get off me.
[Morrow] When is a machine not a machine?
"Of all delectable islands
the Neverland is the snuggest
and most compact…
[birds chirping]
[Kavalier] …not large and sprawly, you know,
with tedious distances between
one adventure and another,
but nicely crammed.
When you play at it by day
with the chairs and tablecloth,
it is not in the least alarming,
but in the two minutes before you
go to sleep it becomes very nearly real.
That is why there are night-lights."
[Slightly] We're not friends.
[Morrow] No, I suppose not.
But I want to be.
[Slightly] Friends don't lie.
You said you were Prodigy.
Well, I didn't know
if you were a villain or a hero.
Hero.
Me too.
And since we're both heroes,
I need your help.
Get something and bring it
to me, okay? An egg.
You don't have eggs where you are?
It's not that kind of egg.
A monster egg.
Such a smart boy.
[Slightly] No, I can't. I can't.
[whispers, stammers]
That would be stealing.
But wait. How can you steal from a thief?
[Slightly] Is this another riddle?
A moral inquiry. Do you know
the difference between right and wrong?
[Slightly] I think so.
Well, if that egg belongs to me
and somebody takes it,
how can it be wrong to take it back?
[Slightly] They fixed me here, you know?
Like, Boy Kavalier. This… This is my home.
[sighs]
Now you're talking about loyalty.
That's a very different principle.
People do all kinds of terrible things
in the name of loyalty. No.
If you want to do the moral thing,
you'll help me get back what you stole.
Think of it as restitution.
What's "recstitution"?
It means making things right.
You want to make things right, don't you?
Can I talk to someone about it?
Like Smee or someone?
He always knows the answers to things.
[Morrow] No, you can't talk to anyone.
That would hurt me
and what do we know about hurting people?
It's wrong?
Yes, very good.
Can I trust you? We need to trust each
other if we're gonna make this work.
So I'm going to tell you my name.
It's Kumi. Kumi Morrow.
[chuckles] Kumi? It's a nice name.
It's Ghanaian.
Remind me of your name again?
Slightly.
-No, silly. Your real name.
-Oh.
Not… Not supposed to say.
Well, how can I trust you
if you won't tell me your name?
It's Aarush.
Aarush what?
[Slightly] Singh.
♪Aarush what? ♪
[laughs] No, like Singh with an H.
It's Indian.
Well then, Aarush Singh…
Let's figure out how
you're gonna make things right.
Do you know why there are
three monkeys on your wall?
What?
Mizaru sees no evil.
Kikazaru hears no evil.
Iwazaru speaks no evil.
They're figures in Buddhist teaching
about avoiding evil thoughts and deeds,
but over the years they've come
to represent something else.
Do you know what that is?
No.
If I did something evil,
would you report me?
-I--
-If I…
hurt or caused others to be hurt,
would you do something to stop me
or would you look the other way?
[Morrow] Careful.
Everything okay?
Yes. It's just, um… [breathes shakily]
Is this a test?
That's what being an adult is.
A constant test.
I would stand up for my friends.
[breathes deeply]
Good.
[sheep bleats]
[bleats]
[squelching]
-[bleating]
-[squelching]
[bleats]
[beating and squelching stop]
[growling]
[snarls, growling]
Fascinating.
Yeah, the wavy lines
are totally different now.
Those are gamma waves.
Problem solving, concentration.
See how they've increased?
-[Tootles] Mm-hmm.
-[sheep fluttering]
-This creature is highly intelligent.
-[fluttering continues]
Look how it's watching us.
[growls]
-If one of those ever escapes--
-Glass half full, kid.
Yeah? We talked about this.
[ball thuds]
[squeals]
Hey. Hey.
[growling]
Mmm.
Me.
Yeah.
[birds chirping]
Arthur, what is it?
[huffs] Arthur, where are you taking me?
I don't understand
why we had to leave the lab. What?
Are you serious?
Darling, can you please just
explain to me what's going on?
And what are we doing here?
This isn't science.
We're-We're halfway through
beta testing the hybrids,
and he brings in, who knows
how many alien species. [stammers]
It is a multi-world corporation.
I think we can do two things at once.
Yeah, but she's not ready.
Wendy, I mean, or any of them.
I mean, this-this morning proves that,
that the data isn't there.
And we mapped out the steps. The--
[indistinct through intercom]
The control groups, the system checks.
He sends them to a crash site into combat.
Yes, he breaks the rules. He takes risks.
Maybe that's why he's so…
[chuckles] …far ahead.
Yeah, but that's not science.
I mean, I don't care how rich you get.
Something is or it isn't.
Quantum mechanics.
-Okay, that's--
-Light is a particle and a wave.
Yes, theoretically, yeah.
But-But we took the minds of
children and put them in synthetic bodies.
That's not theoretical.
I mean, if we did this wrong,
best case, we've got a bunch of AIs
running around
thinking that they're human.
Worst case, we killed six kids.
That is not something
we're flippant about, ever.
I hear you. I just--
I'm worried and I…
I need you to hear that.
Not as a scientist, but as your husband.
I do, I do.
Okay, then we need to stick to
the protocols, reevaluate the risks.
I think we need to think about
what's gonna happen
if this whole thing goes to hell.
Listen…
I'll make dinner tonight, okay?
Love dumplings.
We'll sit and talk this through.
We'll figure it out.
[humming]
Hey, sweetheart.
I have good news.
Such good news.
I'm pregnant.
What?
I'm gonna have a baby.
No, that-- that's-- that's impossible.
You're a machine.
I'm not a machine. Why would you say that?
No, of course not, baby.
[Dame Sylvia] He didn't mean that.
You're just too young to have a child.
Well, it's true.
I woke up this morning and I just knew.
It's not all those horrible things
he was saying about me.
What's inside of me, controlling me.
Metal and silicone.
It's a baby.
Wow, that's… [chuckles] …big news.
Why don't we go to my office
and we can talk.
How have you been feeling?
Pretty tired.
This being pregnant thing is hard work.
[Dame Sylvia] We haven't talked
in a while.
And now you have this feeling.
It's not just a feeling.
I'm gonna have a baby.
[Dame Sylvia] Well, that's interesting.
Can you tell me…
Do you know how babies are made?
God brings them.
[Dame Sylvia] Yes, on some level.
But there's also a process,
a physical process
between a man and a woman.
A biological process.
I know about all that.
I grew up on a farm.
[Dame Sylvia] Oh, well, then you know.
A man and a woman,
their bodies fit together
and the man's sperm fertilizes
the woman's egg.
Then, the embryo grows into a baby.
Except for Jesus.
His mommy didn't do that, and he was born.
You know what,
I'm starting to realize that we didn't…
[smacks lips, inhales sharply, chuckles]
In all the busyness of trying to make sure
that everything went right
with your transition, all of you,
we never really talked about
your new bodies…
[humming]
…how they work, how they're different.
You know it's different, right?
Your new body.
[humming]
It's big.
It is, but it's not just the size.
I'm talking about on the inside.
Let me show you a diagram.
I don't want to look at that.
-Here.
-I said no.
Okay.
It's a girl, I think. Clarissa.
-Nibs.
-[Nibs] That's her name.
What she wants to be called.
What happened at the towers?
[growls]
I don't wanna talk about that.
[Dame Sylvia] Curly said you
were really brave.
I said I don't want to talk about it.
Those creatures can't hurt you,
you know that, right?
-They're all locked up.
-I said stop talking.
[gasps, breathing heavily]
All right, sweetheart. I'm sorry.
Do you want to have some tea?
I was thinking about having
a… [stammers] …cup of tea.
[breathing heavily]
[whispering] I'm sorry.
I got those, uh, new flavor strips
that you asked for,
the chamomile and mint.
I like apple cinnamon.
Oh, apple cinnamon, yeah. Okay, yeah,
I have that too. [breathing heavily]
If it's a boy,
what do you think about Trevor?
Trevor, that's… Good name.
[chuckles] Strong.
Oh, sweetheart,
I… [chuckles] …I didn't realize
I was meant to be meeting Mr. Kavalier.
These gentlemen will help you
-back to your room, okay?
-Hmm. Okay.
Can I keep him?
[chuckling] Of course.
And, listen, we'll talk again soon, okay?
-I've missed our talks.
-Okay.
[breathes shakily]
Get her back to her room.
Secure the door.
Tell your supervisor
we have a level three event.
He'll know what to do.
-Yes, ma'am.
-[breathing heavily]
[Hermit] You wanted to see me?
I thought we might discuss
your future with this company.
My unit, sir, specifically Rashidi,
Siberian, are they okay?
That information is confidential.
To be completely frank,
so is the information about Wendy.
Marcy. My sister's name is Marcy.
So you believe she's your sister?
She has her memories, her sense of humor.
Doesn't that make her Marcy?
Actually, that's something
we'd like to know too.
From you.
From me?
We'd like confirmation
from someone who knew her well
that the transition was a success.
She thinks she's my sister.
What do you think?
I think this conversation's over.
It's a condition of your employment
that you answer
all questions put to you by a superior.
Well, then, I quit.
Of course.
As this is a private island, we'll have to
get you on the first shuttle back home.
Confidentiality, you understand.
I should tell you that
if you're no longer employed by us,
then all contact with the unit
you call your sister
-will be terminated.
-No. [grunts] No.
Also, as your body keeps reminding you,
you have a new lung.
Whilst it comes courtesy of
the Prodigy Corporation, it isn't free.
You could work off the price here,
assessing Wendy, redeploy
and pay it off with a lifetime contract,
or simply go home, and we'll bill you.
Did you really download
my sister's consciousness into that body?
Is it her?
Those are two different questions.
One is practical and the other,
well, that's the real existential crux,
and, I should add, the difference between
a trillion-dollar business
and a blanket with sleeves.
A what?
An invention that no one wanted.
So, are you still an employee of
the Prodigy Corporation,
or shall I have security
remove you from the island?
No, no.
[breathes heavily] I'm your man.
Excellent.
And when can I take her home?
Let me be clear about something,
Prodigy Medic Hermit.
The unit you call your sister is
the property of the Prodigy Corporation.
She is a prototype for
a transhuman product
which, once refined,
will create human immortality.
This makes her the next evolutionary step
between our animal past
and our transhuman future.
There's no universe in which
you get to take her home.
Are we clear?
-She is still a human being.
-No.
She's not.
Not anymore.
[Rashidi] Smell that? What is that?
I don't know. It smells like a mix of
bad luck and loser.
[Hermit] How the hell?
[chuckles]
[Hermit] So, what, you… you work here now?
[Rashidi through screen]
Yeah. Whole squad.
[Siberian] Well, what's left of us.
[Boy Kavalier] Weird day.
I'm supposed to meet with Sylvia.
[Boy Kavalier] Have a seat.
Pirates or Indians?
Um…
When you fought the alien,
was it more like fighting pirates
or Indians?
[chuckling] What?
It's Peter Pan.
Wait, the crocodile.
You fought the crocodile,
and now you can hear the clock, you know?
Tick, tick, tick, tick, tick, tick.
It was hurting Joe.
Oh, right, the brother.
What do you think they're saying?
The aliens.
You shouldn't have cut them open.
[stammers] They… They said that?
No, I… I don't know.
How would you feel if they cut you open?
Or, uh, stuck to my face or drank my blood
or popped out my eyeball
and burrowed into my brain.
I mean, they would if they could,
you know, so why not just cut them open?
Should we let him stay, you think?
The brother?
Give him access to all this? You?
Please. He's nice.
[clicks tongue, stammers] It's nice
if you like brothers, which I don't.
Or fathers or, ugh, mothers, you know.
[grunts] Always telling us what to do.
Why do you think she wanted them?
Yutani, the aliens.
I think we should send them back.
[Boy Kavalier] Because they hurt you?
Because it's wrong keeping them.
Uh… No. I'll tell you who
we should send back. Your brother.
[clicks tongue]
-[Wendy] Please don't.
-[Boy Kavalier] None of the others
get to have brothers.
What makes you so special?
I'm not special. I just…
-Please.
-Oh, come on. Come on. [scoffs]
What kind of intellectual argument
is "please"?
No, I'm sorry. We should send him back
on the next plane home.
I mean, if you think about it…
[inhales deeply] …he didn't even come
visit you when you were sick.
Joe was working. He was far away.
[imitating Hermit] Oh, my God.
It's too far. It's too hard.
All I know is if I was your brother,
I'd find a way to be there.
I tell you what.
If you help me figure out
what the aliens are saying,
I'll let you keep him. Okay?
But the minute he becomes a distraction--
He won't. I promise.
Pinky promise.
[smacks lips] Okay.
Away with you.
[growling]
[electronic screeching]
You know what?
Hmm?
Can I change my name?
-You want to talk about this now?
-Um…
I'm a grown man. A-A scientist.
I-I want a real name.
Our leader named you when you were born.
I know, but that's like a--
It's like a code name like Sport or Chief.
It's-It's not what you call a man.
You know, a serious man.
What would you like to be called?
Well, I was thinking about… [stammers]
…scientists.
You know, like famous thinkers.
And I was thinking Isaac.
-After--
-Isaac Newton.
Yes, I think that's all right.
[sighs, sniffles]
-Oh, Hey.
-Hey.
I was just, uh…
I'm doing proper science now.
Um, Kirsh really relies on me.
Kirsh. Wow. Well, that's awesome.
-Yeah. And I've got a new name.
-Uh-huh.
Isaac, after the old-time scientist.
[chuckles] Where'd you get that?
Gave it to myself.
Wow, we can do that?
I don't know about "can," but I did.
Anyway, Kirsh said it was okay, so…
I"m-I'm helping too, you know. Um…
Arthur said that
he needs something from the lab.
Oh. Cool. What?
Huh?
Yeah, what does Arthur need from the lab?
Oh. Oh, it was, um…
[stutters]
[inhales deeply] Okay, well,
we're gonna go play some games.
So come.
And then you'll remember, probably.
Actually, I'm just gonna take a walk.
Just clear my head.
You sure?
Yeah, I'm just, uh, you know…
I'll see you later. Bye.
[Isaac] Cool.
[typing]
[Slightly] Hey, uh, hello?
It's me.
I'm not sure how this works, but, um…
can you hear me?
-[Morrow] I can hear you.
-Oh.
Okay, well, great.
I-I checked it out, you know, the lab.
And there's just no way, you know.
You're a very clever boy.
You'll figure it out.
[Slightly] Oh, no, no. W-What I'm trying
to say is that… I can't do it.
Can't or won't?
They're my friends.
[sighs] So won't.
[Slightly] I'm sorry, Kumi.
[sighs] Aarush,
I'm afraid "sorry" doesn't work.
You know, it's funny you called.
I was just talking about you.
With your mother.
What?
She thought you were dead.
Isn't that awful?
-Mummy?
-[Morrow] Oh, she can't hear you.
This is our private line.
But you know what she told me?
Your brothers will be home soon.
I can't wait to meet them.
No, no, no, no. Please, please, please.
[chuckling] Oh. Now it's "please"?
You know, Aarush,
I really wanted us to be friends.
[Slightly stutters] We are, right?
We are friends.
I hope so,
but friends help each other, right?
I'll help.
Well, that's great. What a relief.
He's gonna help.
[Slightly] I just don't know how,
you know? Like, th-there's just one of me
and there's so many guards
and they have guns and--
[Morrow] I'll tell you
what you're gonna do.
Instead of sneaking out an egg,
you're gonna sneak in a person.
[Slightly] A person?
Into the lab. Anyone you like.
Take them to see the eggs.
Get them good and close.
Why?
Well, the egg is gonna hatch
and something's gonna come out.
Don't worry. It doesn't want you.
Something's gonna come out
and attach itself to the person's face.
And he or she is gonna fall down,
and you need to find
some place quiet to keep them.
Not long, just a day or two.
And the thing on the person's face
is gonna fall off.
And they're gonna wake up.
And that-that-that's
when I bring them to you?
[Morrow] Exactly.
[Morrow through screen]
But you'll have to be quick, okay?
[Slightly stammering] Okay, but how do I--
[Morrow] Don't worry, I'll be close.
You call me and I'll meet you.
What happens to the person I choose?
Well, they'll have a bad couple of days,
for sure,
but I'll make sure they're comfortable.
Understand?
No. I-I don't understand,
like, how… how do I… how do I choose?
Oh, looks like
your mom wants to say something.
Did you want to say something to Aarush?
[Slightly's mother] Aarush.
Mummy?
We love you, beta.
[crying] You know, every day your brothers
and me talk about you.
-Aarush--
-[Morrow shushes]
Mummy?
[Morrow] Isn't that sweet?
But I've gotta go,
you know what you've gotta do.
Let's say you have 24 hours to choose
someone and get them in front of the eggs.
-[breathing heavily, stuttering] Twenty--
-[Morrow] A day, I'm saying.
-A day. Okay.
-[Morrow] This time tomorrow.
Hey, remember before?
When we talked and you said all that stuff
about how you'd do anything you had to
to protect your parents?
This is that. Are we clear?
[whispers] Yes, we're clear. Okay.
Okay. Great.
You're doing great. Now, go get 'em.
[breathing shakily]
[beeping, ticking]
[birds chirping]
-[Smee] No, no, no. No.
-[Wendy] No, not that one.
-No. Try this one.
-I don't get to choose?
[whispers] Just try it.
It's good. It's good. You'll like it.
Tastes like motor oil. Jesus.
[Wendy] But it doesn't really have
a flavor. It's like a sequence to it.
[Isaac] It's a line of code, actually.
It's like a subroutine that triggers
a synthetic memory of a flavor.
-[snores]
-[Isaac] Like script.
Smarty-pants.
Well, I've been reading a lot.
You know, Arthur has these computer chips,
like, um… like a library.
You just upload them
and suddenly all the information
from the book is suddenly in your head.
-Wait, we can do that?
-[Isaac] Mm-hmm. Anything you want.
I'm learning zoology and advanced biology,
so I can help Kirsh out in the lab.
Can I ask you a question?
Of course.
What's the Five?
The boss,
he keeps talking about "the Five."
[Hermit] Uh, well, the old planet had
something called governments,
where people used to… They would vote for
who they wanted making decisions, right?
It didn't work.
So these five corporations, they rose up
and they apparently…
they fixed all the problems.
Now they work together to run things.
Prodigy, Weyland-Yutani…
-[Hermit] Threshold, Dynamic, Lynch.
-And Lynch. Yeah.
And the ship that crashed,
it was Yutani's, and we took it.
-And they're mad.
-[inhales deeply]
-Mmm.
-So, they're probably asking the Five
to step in and get their stuff back.
Their creatures?
Yeah.
[Isaac] They're life-forms.
We've learned so much from them already.
Well, if you love them so much,
why don't you just marry them?
-[mocking]
-[laughs]
[laughs] Hey, hey. We're eating
ice cream and we're talking.
How come he's here?
He's my brother.
I've got brothers too.
-We've all got brothers and mothers.
-Slightly.
And if they're not here,
-he shouldn't be either.
-[Wendy] Hey, you're being rude.
You're not the boss of us.
I'm the oldest.
No. Curly's what, like 12?
And Isaac too.
[Hermit] I agree.
Your families should be here, all of them.
Instead of having funerals,
they should have had parties.
You were dying and now look at you.
Yeah, we should… we should ask
to see our families.
No. Demand.
Yeah. See my mom.
No. They'll get mad
and might send us away.
-And I like it here.
-Me too. I mean,
we get respect here,
and they've made us into something.
[Curly] Yeah.
I'm gonna go.
The boy genius said to go to the lab,
so I'm gonna go.
You don't have to.
I want to.
[chirring]
-[chirring continues]
-[Wendy chirrs]
[chirring continues]
[Wendy chirring]
[humming]
[vocalizing]
[vocalizing stops]
[screeching]
[screeching continues]
[Wendy breathing heavily]
[screeches]
["Ocean Size" playing]